[Music]
on today's episode of willa ice cream we
are just doing coffee
i'm a big coffee drinker i can't leave
the house without one and probably can't
survive the day without another three
four or five but will it churn in the
cheapest ice cream machine i could find
on amazon who knows let's try it now
first we've got to do is make a cup of
coffee and let it cool down
i'm going to use nescafe azira this is a
grind smith
combo so there's a collaboration between
them this is really nice
i don't normally use cream this is a
very american thing cream and coffee but
my thinking is
you know we gotta try and get this as
creamy somehow i'm not gonna attempt to
put this one in the freezer we're just
gonna
make the coffee get it cold stick it in
the ice cream machine and see what it
tastes like so
let's just get stuck in cattle's just
boiled let's make a cup of coffee
[Music]
i'll see you in about an hour
and we're back
it's stone cold
it looks rank
let's get the ice cream machine out
stick it on here
and do the thing with the stuff
[Music]
[Applause]
put that in there
and let's
let's go
[Music]
hey
this thing's been going for
30 minutes
i think
[Music]
the answer is
no
so
will your morning cup of coffee made
with cream turn into ice cream try
putting it in an ice cream machine no is
the answer to that thanks for watching
see you next time
[Music]
[Applause]
you